Guide to the William J. Baumol Papers, circa 1940-1995 (bulk 1950-1990)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, 1947-1995
  - 1977-1980 (Box W3)
    - Scale Economies and Intertemporal ( 1979) (Box W3)
    - The Price Iso-Return Locus ( 1979) (Box W3)
    - On Some Microeconomic Issues ( 1979) (Box W3)
    - Quasi-Permanence of Price Reductions ( 1979) (Box W3)
    - Planning and Dual Values of Linearized ( 1979) (Box W3)
    - Newspaper Editorials ( 1979-1983) (Box W3)
    - Various Papers ( 1979) (Box W3)
    - Baumol-Blinder Introductory Economics Text ( 1979-1982) (Box W3)
    - On the Finances of the Performing Arts ( 1980) (Box W3)
    - Productivity, Rising R&D Costs ( 1980) (2 folders) (Box W3)
    - Unprofitable Energy ( 1980) (Box W3)
    - Profitability and Energy Output ( 1980) (Box W3)
    - Various Papers ( 1980) (Box W3)
  - 1981-1982 (Box W4)
    - Straddles ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - Superfairness Theory and Rationing Policy ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - Peak Pricing, Congestion, and Fairness ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - Subsidies to New Energy Sources ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - On the Regulation of Utilities ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - Entrepreneurship and the Sociopolitical ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - Contestable Markets: An Uprising ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - Various Papers ( 1981) (Box W4)
    - Government as a Catalyst for Private Pursuit ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - On the Theory of Perfectly Contestable Markets ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - On Inflation and the Arts ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - A Paradox in the Measurement of Interindustry ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - On My Sculptures of Carved Wood ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - Marx and the Iron Law of Wages ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - Deregulation and the New Contestability Analysis ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - Contestable Markets and the Theory of Industry ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - Towards an Analysis of Entrepreneurship ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - Models for Systematic Evaluation of ( 1982) (Box W4)
    - The Income Distribution Frontier ( 1982) (Box W4)
  - 1982-1983 (Box W5)
    - Various ( 1982) (Box W5)
    - Productivity in Higher Education ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Towards a Theory of Public Enterprise ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Introduction to Reinecius and Themes that Emerged ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Fairness Book ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - On the Career of a Microeconomist ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - On Interindustry Differences in Absolute Productivity ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Feedback Models, R&D, Information ( 1983) (2 folders) (Box W5)
    - Growth Policy and the Services ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Feedback from Productivity Growth ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Deregulation and the Theory of Contestable Markets ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Industry Structure Analysis and Public ( 1983) (Box W5)
    - Various Papers, (1983) (2 folders) (Box W5)
  - 1984-1995 (Box W6)
    - Various Papers, (1984) (2 folders) (Box W6)
    - The Mass Media and the Cost Disease ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - Input and Output Composition Changes ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - On My Attitudes: Sociopolitical and Methodological ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - Use of Antitrust to Subvert Competition and on Productivity Growth in the Long Run ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - Productivity and Related Variables ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - Palgrave Entries ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - Wheatsheaf Prefaces ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - Unbalanced Growth Revisited ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - The Future of the Theatre ( 1984) (Box W6)
    - Rebirth of a Fallen Leader: Italy ( 1985) (Box W6)
    - Productivity Book ( 1986) (Box W6)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism ( 1986) (Box W6)
    - Antitrust Policy and High Technology ( 1988) (Box W6)
    - Antitrust: Source of Dynamic and ... ( 1990) (Box W6)
    - Volume on Entrepreneurship ( 1990) (Box W6)
    - Scale Economies ( 1992) (Box W6)
    - Reswitching, Social Discount Rate, and Environmental Protection ( 1995) (Box W6)
  - Miscellaneous/No Date/and Printed Material (Box W7)
    - Various Papers ( 1968-1979) (Box W7)
    - Various Papers ( 1982-1983) (Box W7)
    - Competitive Interdependence in Decision Making ( undated) (Box W7)
    - Misc. Speeches ( undated) (Box W7)
    - Various Papers ( undated) (Box W7)
    - Publication List ( 1947-1987) (Box W7)
    - Printed Material:
      - C.V. Starr Center Discussion Paper Series ( 1975-1985) (5 folders) (Box W7)
      - An Introduction to Linear Programming (Box W7)
      - Lectures in Economic Theory (Box W7)
      - Superfairness: Applications and Theory (Box W7)
      - Economic Dynamics: An Introduction (Box W7)
      - Business Behavior, Value, and Growth (Box W7)
      - Contestable Markets and the Theory of Industry Structure (Box W7)
- Subject Files Series, 1942-1989
  - Project Files Subseries, 1942-1982
    Includes grants, proposals, reports, and statistical data output. Folder titles are the originals except for the Government, Industry, and Performing Arts files, since most of this material was received as loose papers. Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - Applied Theory of Fairness ( 1980s) (Box S1)
    - Baumol as Artist ( various dates) (Box S1)
    - Book Proposal: Adventures in Chinese Grocery Shopping ( undated) (Box S1)
    - Committee for Economic Development ( 1982) (Box S1)
    - Committee on Contracting with Publishers ( 1980-1983) (2 folders) (Box S1)
    - Commission on New Technological Uses of Copyrighted Work ( 1976-1977) (2 folders) (Box S1)
    - Cookbook for NSF/DSI ( 1976) (Box S1)
    - Dept. of Agriculture Reports ( 1942-1943 and 1952) (Box S1)
    - Economic Policy Council ( 1970-1974) (Box S1)
    - Government Projects:
      - Joint Economic Committee ( 1958) (Box S1)
      - Senate Judiciary Committee ( 1981) (Box S1)
      - Senate Public Works Committee on Materials Policy ( 1976) (Box S1)
      - Senate Subcommittee on Employment and Productivity ( 1982) (Box S1)
      - State of New York Assembly ( 1984) (Box S1)
      - Subcommittee on the Activities of Regulatory Agencies relating to Small Businesses ( 1968) (Box S1)
      - Telecommunications Bill ( 1982) (Box S1)
      - US House of Representatives ( 1981-1982 and undated) (Box S1)
    - Grants, misc. ( various dates) (Box S1)
    - Industry Consulting:
      - P. Ballatine and Sons ( 1963) (Box S1)
      - Canadian Railroads ( 1976) (Box S1)
      - Carpenter Steel Company ( 1957) (Box S1)
      - Cost Indices ( 1981) (Box S1)
      - Dept. of the Navy ( 1958-1963) (Box S1)
      - General Foods ( 1963) (Box S1)
      - Media Selection ( 1963) (Box S1)
      - Monsanto Chemical Company ( 1957) (Box S1)
      - Morgan Stanley ( 1963-1964) (Box S2)
      - Philadelphia Retail Market ( 1960) (Box S2)
      - Southern Railway ( 1963-1965) (Box S2)
      - Wharton School of Finance and Commerce ( 1960) (Box S2)
    - Interaction between Price Changes and Government Regulation ( 1977) (Box S2)
    - Joint Council on Economic Education ( undated) (Box S2)
    - Lazarsfeld Project ( 1953) (Box S2)
    - Mc Caleb Seiler Publishing Co. ( 1969-70) (Box S2)
    - Microeconomics Research Fund ( 1977-1982) (2 folders) (Box S2)
    - New York University Subcommittee on Graduate Education ( 1983) (Box S2)
    - Performing Arts and Economics:
      - Art Finances ( 1980-1985) (Box S2)
      - Artistic Deficit Study ( 1985-1990) (4 folders) (Box S2)
      - Economic Development and the Performing Arts ( 1982) (Box S2)
      - Financial Data ( 1975-1989) (Box S2)
      - Miscellaneous ( various dates) (Box S2)
      - National Endowment for the Arts ( 1975-1989) (Box S2)
      - Papers ( 1986 and undated) (Box S2)
      - US-USSR Arts Study ( 1989-1990) (4 folders) (Box S2)
    - Pfizer Grant ( 1980-1981) (Box S2)
    - Rescuing the Free Market from its Constituents ( 1983) (Box S2)
    - Scale Economies and Public Attributes of Information ( 1974-1977) (5 folders) (Box S3)
    - Sloan Seminar ( 1978-1982) (Box S3)
    - Towards a Theory of Determination of Market Form ( 1977-1980) (Box S3)
  - Teaching Materials Subseries, 1946-89
    Includes lecture notes, course syllabi, exams and problem sets. Arranged alphabetically.
    - Baumol as Student; includes four undated notebooks (Box S3)
    - Description and Analysis of the Price System ( 1989) (Box S3)
    - Economic Dynamics and Welfare Theory ( 1946-1949) (Box S3)
    - Economics of Antitrust ( 1978) (Box S3)
    - Exams ( 1950-1959) (Box S3)
    - Exams ( 1960-1969) (Box S3)
    - Exams ( 1970-1979) (Box S3)
    - Exams ( 1980-1989) (Box S3)
    - History of Economic Thought ( 1979-1988) (2 folders) (Box S3)
    - Industrial Organization ( undated) (Box S3)
    - Miscellaneous ( various dates) (Box S3)
    - Regulation Lectures ( 1983) (Box S3)
    - Robbins Lectures on Classical Economics ( undated) (Box S3)
    - Transparencies ( undated) (Box S3)
  - Research Files Subseries, undated
    - History of Economics: (Box S4)
      - Cantillon (Box S4)
      - Cournot, A. (Box S4)
      - Marshall, Alfred (Box S4)
      - Marx, Karl (5 folders) (Box S4)
      - Ricardo, David (Box S4)
      - Robbins Manuscript (Box S4)
      - Smith, Adam (Box S4)
      - Wicksell, Knut (Box S4)
    - Industrial Organization:
      - Contestability Theory (5 folders) (Box S4)
      - Predatory Pricing (2 folders) (Box S4)
      - Price Flexibility (Box S4)
    - Fairness (11 folders) (Box S5)
    - Productivity/ Entrepreneurship (3 of 11 folders) (Box S5)
    - Productivity/ Entrepreneurship (folders 4-11) (Box S6)
    - General:
      - Chaos (Box S6)
      - Comparative Statics (Box S6)
      - Current Problems ( undated) (Box S6)
      - Deceleration of British Growth ( 1873-1913) by W. Arthur Lewis ( 1967) (Box S6)
      - Finance (Box S6)
      - Mozart (3 folders) (Box S6)
      - Non Linear Differential Equations (Box S6)
      - Portfolio Theory (Box S6)
- Legal Testimony Series
  Includes sworn testimony, affidavits, drafts, correspondence and papers prepared for counsel. Arranged by date. Material that was clearly marked "privileged and confidential" is noted below; however, without examining every document, it is impossible to conclude that the list is complete or that other documents do not make reference to the confidential material. Researchers wishing to use this series must sign a release form provided by the reference staff.
  - Civil Actions Subseries, 1967-1994 (RESTRICTED)
    - 1967, 5227, Louisville and Nashville Railroad v. United States (Box LT1)
    - 1977, 74C 633, MCI v. AT&T (2 folders) (Box LT1)
    - 74-3599 (RJK) and 74-3600 (RJK) USA v. CBS, Inc. and USA v. ABC, Inc. (Box LT1)
    - 1981, 74-1698, United States v. AT&T (Box LT1)
    - 1981, 79 Civ. 6996, Sharon Steel Corporation (Box LT1)
    - 3AN-79-1903 and 3AN-80-1542, Atlantic Richfield Co. v. State of Alaska (Box LT1)
    - 82 Civ. 1093 (JES) and 1394, 1737, 2746, 6399 and 83 Civ. 3138 (JES), Low Density Polyethylene Resins Antitrust Litigation (1 folder, 1 bound item) (Box LT1)
    - 1984, G-93-265, TCA Building Co. v Northwestern Resources Co. (1 folder, 1 bound item) (Box LT1)
    - 1986, Midtec v. C&NW (Box LT1)
    - 1987, 86-5428, Chlorine and Caustic Soda Antitrust Litigation (FILED UNDER SEAL) (Box LT1)
    - 1988, C.A. no 10319, Grand Metropolitan PLC v. Pillsbury Co. (Box LT1)
    - 1989, 88-Civ-3474 (JMcL), City of New York v. US Dept. of Commerce (Box LT1)
    - 1989, MDL 587, Lower Lake Erie Iron Ore Antitrust Litigation (2 folders) (Box LT1)
    - 1989, MDL-667-ER (TX), Air Passenger Computer Reservation Antitrust Litigation (2 folders, 1 bound item) (Box LT1)
    - 1991, 38302s, US Dept. of Energy v. Ohio Railroad Co. (Box LT1)
    - 1993, Consolidated Rail Corp. (Box LT1)
    - 1994, 82-0192 HHG, USA v. Western Electric and AT&T (2 bound items) (Box LT2)
    - 1994, CV94-3682 (ERK), Bell Atlantic, NYNEX v. AT&T (Box LT2)
  - Federal Communications Commission Subseries, 1966-1994 and undated (RESTRICTED)
    Note: Dockets 16258 are "Qualified Proceedings".
    - 1966-1969, No. 16258 (Box LT2)
    - 1967, No. 16258, American Telephone and Telegraph Co. ( AT&T) (Box LT2)
    - Official Proceedings (7 folders) (Box LT2)
    - 1974, AT&T Correspondence (3 folders) (Box LT2)
    - 1966-1975, Nos. 16258, 18128, 19919, 20376, 20288, Direct Testimony Exhibits (2 folders) (Box LT2)
    - Nos. 18128, 18684, 18718 (Box LT2)
    - 1976, No. 18128, Memorandum Opinion and Order (Box LT2)
    - Circa 1970s, Miscellaneous Testimony (Box LT2)
    - 1973-1990, AT&T Papers and Correspondence (Box LT3)
    - 1973-1991, AT&T Papers and Correspondence (Box LT3)
    - 1981-1986, AT&T Papers and Correspondence (Box LT3)
    - 1983, BC 82-345, Financial Interest Rule and Syndication (1 folder, 2 bound items) (Box LT3)
    - 1994, CC Docket 87-313 Policy and Rules Concerning Rates for Dominant Carriers (Box LT3)
    - undated, Transparencies (Box LT3)
    - undated, Miscellaneous documents (Box LT3)
  - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission Subseries, 1983-1993 (RESTRICTED)
    - 1983, OR78-1-014 and 016, TransAlaska Pipeline System (Box LT3)
    - 1985, OR79-1-000 and 002, Williams Pipelines Co. (Box LT3)
    - 1986, IS85-15-000, Southern Pacific Pipelines, Inc. (Box LT3)
    - 1988, IS87-14-000, Buckeye Pipeline Company (PROTECTED MATERIALS) (Box LT3)
    - 1993, RM93-11-000, Revisions to Oil Pipeline Regulations (Box LT3)
  - Federal Trade Commission Subseries, 1982-1986 (RESTRICTED) (Box LT4)
    - 1982, 9135, B.A.T. Industries and Appleton Papers Inc. (Box LT4)
    - 1985, 9157, Echlin Manufacturing Co. and Borg-Warner Corp. (Box LT4)
    - 1986, 86-1764, Coca-Cola Company (Box LT4)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission Subseries, 1970-1993 and undated (RESTRICTED)
    - 1970, 34013(1), Cost Standards in Intramodal Rate Proceedings (Box LT4)
    - 1973, 27353(1), Determination of Compensation (1 folder, 1 bound item) (Box LT4)
    - 1980, 9222, Conrail Surcharge on Pulpboard (Box LT4)
    - 1981, 37063 and 357, Increased Rates on Coal (Box LT4)
    - 1981, No. 30 000, Union Pacific Corp. (2 folders, 1 bound item) (Box LT4)
    - 1982-1988, No. 292, Railroad Cost Recovery Procedures (3 bound items) (Box LT4)
    - 1982, No. 36988, Alternative Methods of Accounting for Railroad Track Structures (Box LT4)
    - 1981-1986, No. 393 (1), Standards for Railroad Revenue Adequacy (1 folder, 4 bound items), cont. in box IV 5 (Box LT4)
    - 1983, No. 30 300, CSX Corp. v. American Commercial Lines, Inc. (1 folder, 2 bound items) (Box LT5)
    - 1983, No. 347 (1), Coal Rate Guidelines Nationwide (2 folders, 3 bound items), cont. in box 6 (Box LT5)
    - 1984, No. 30 500, Norfolk Southern Corp. v. North American Van Lines (Box LT6)
    - 1985, No. 445 (1), Intramodal Rail Competition (1 folder, 1 bound item) (Box LT6)
    - 1985, No. 346 (8), Exemption from Regulation (2 bound items) (Box LT6)
    - 1985, No. 30 400, Sante Fe Southern Pacific Corp. (1 folder; 6 bound items) (Box LT6)
    - 1985, No. 456, Staggers Rail Act of 1980 (Box LT6)
    - 1985, No. 38676 (Box LT6)
    - 1986, No. 38783, Omaha Public Power v. Burlington Northern Railroad (Box LT6)
    - 1985, Chessie Railroad System: Correspondence (Box LT6)
    - 1987, Nos. 37809 and 37815s, Burlington Northern Inc., (2 bound items) (Box LT6)
    - 1987, No. 38301S, Coal Trading Corp. v. The B&O Railroad Co. (Box LT7)
    - 1987-1994, No. 347(2), Rate Guidelines-Non coal Proceedings (2 bound items) (Box LT7)
    - 1990, No. 37063 and 38025s, Rate Reasonableness Issues (1 bound item) (Box LT7)
    - 1991, No. 30 000 (16), St. Louis Southwestern Railway (1 folder, 1 bound item) (Box LT7)
    - 1992, No. 22218, Atchison, Topeka and Sante Fe Railway Co. (Box LT7)
    - 1993, 21215 (5), Seaboard Airline Railroad Co. (Box LT7)
    - 1993, 32133(2), Union Pacific (FILED UNDER SEAL) (Box LT7)
  - Public Utilities Subseries, 1972-1994 (RESTRICTED)
    - 1972, No. 722-153, Dept. of Public Utilities State of New Jersey (Box LT7)
    - 1974, No. 2-U-7423, Public Service Commission of Wisconsin (Box LT7)
    - 1975, No. 26775, New York State Public Service Commission (2 folders) (Box LT7)
    - 1985, Nos. 86-2, 85-186, 85-212, State of Maine Public Utilities Commission (5 folders) (Box LT7)
    - 1985, No. TC-85-126, TO-85-130 and TO-84-223, Public Service Commission of the State of Missouri (Box LT8)
    - 1987, PUC 870012, Virginia State Corporation Commission (Box LT8)
    - 1988, Nos. 87-0169, 87-0427, 88-0189, 88-0219, 83-0537, and 84-0555, Illinois Commerce Commission (Box LT8)
    - 1989, No. 6669, Public Utilities Commission of Texas (2 folders) (Box LT8)
    - 1992, No. I.87-11-033, Public Utilities Commission of California (Box LT8)
    - 1994, Nos. 93-576-TP-CSS and 93-487-TP-ALT, Public Utilities Commission of Ohio (Box LT8)
    - Miscellaneous papers, various dates (Box LT8)
  - Tax Court Subseries, 1982-1991 and undated (RESTRICTED)
    - 1982, No. 12836-79, G. D. Searle and Co. (Box LT8)
    - 1987, No. 26230-83, Sunstrand Corp. and Subsidiaries (Box LT8)
    - 1991, No. 28860-89, Perkin-Elmer Corp. (Box LT8)
    - undated, Nos. 2674-88 and 23619-88, Yamaha Motor Corp. (Box LT8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1994 and undated (RESTRICTED)
    - Postal Rate Commission (2 folders) (Box LT8)
    - 1983, No. 41686, Civil Aeronautics Board (Box LT8)
    - 1984-1985, Computer Inquiry Project (3 folders) CONFIDENTIAL (Box LT9)
    - 1985 and undated, Fidelity Management and Research Co./Brokerage Commission Rates (3 folders) CONFIDENTIAL (Box LT9)
    - 1985, Railroad Accounting Principles Board (1 folder, 1 bound item) (Box LT9)
    - 1986, No. 29469, AT&T Communications of New York (Box LT9)
    - 1994, New Zealand Telecom (Box LT9)
    - Undated, Nos. 88-07-020, 88-08-051, 89-03-046, AT&T Communications of California (Box LT9)
    - Undated, Copyright Royalty Tribunal (Box LT9)
    - Undated, DPU 18210, New England Telephone and Telegraph Co. (2 folders) (Box LT9)
    - undated, Misc. Testimony and Papers (3 folders) Some FILED UNDER SEAL (Box LT9)
    - Printed Material:
      - Hearings before a subcommittee of the Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives; Subcommittee on HUD independent agencies (Box LT9)
      - Hearings before the Committee on the Judiciary United States Senate on Monopolization and Competition in the Telecommunications Industry (Box LT9)
      - Hearings before the Subcommittee on Telecommunications, Consumer Protection, and Finance of the Committee on Energy and Commerce; House of Representatives (Box LT9)
- Accession 2001-0169, 1964-1990s
  Boxes 2-3 and 12-14 contain sensitive material. Patron must sign a release form before use. Contact a Reference Archivist.
  - Lectures and reserve materials for Economics 506: History of Economic Thought, Economics 541: Industrial Organization and Public Policy, and Economics 102: Micro-Description and Analysis of Price Systems, 1979; Reviews and comments, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Warhol case, NZ, Misc. Cons[ultations], 1991-1995 (Box 2-3)
    Includes sensitive information: legal case files. Patron must sign privacy waiver before use.
  - 6th ed. Baumol-Blinder, 1992 (Box 3-5)
    Correspondence and drafts of each chapter of Economics: Principles and Policy
  - Drafts of articles, 1982-1994 (Box 5-7)
    Also includes biographical information in box 6.
  - Expired grants, 1986-1990 (Box 7-9)
    Mainly Pew Charitable Trust and National Science Foundation.
  - Drafts of essays, newspaper articles, and speeches; book reviews written by Baumol, 1973-1992 (Box 9-11)
  - Drafts of articles, 1986-1990s (Box 12-14)
    Includes testimony for air passenger computer reservation systems antitrust litigation case in box 12.
  - Correspondence, 1964-1978; reviews of Baumol's work and his comments, 1979-1980 and 1974 (Box 15-17)
  - Miscellaneous Baumol/Wolff/Blackman productivity articles, 1979-1988 (Box 17-21)
  - Productivity files (old), 1981-1985 (Box 21-23)
    Including "Sue Anne's Files."
  - Files (drafts), 1989-1993 (Box 24-26)
    Includes drafts of essays and newspaper articles.
  - [Drafts of chapters for] Productivity and American Leadership: The Long View (Box 26-28)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986-1987; reviews and comments file, 1985-1995 (Box 28-32)
  - Legal-size materials (Box 32)
    - Warhol case materials (Box 32)
    - Convergence of productivity Baumol art (Box 32)
- Accession 2001-0170, 1974-1990
  Boxes 1, 5-7 contain sensitive material. Patron must sign a release form before use. Contact a Reference Archivist.
  - Sloan applicants; articles reviewed or read; recommendations, 1980-1987 (Box 1)
    Contains sensitive material. Patron must sign release form before use. Contact a Reference Archivist.
  - Recommendations, 1975-1981; engagements accepted and not accepted, 1984-1988 (Box 2)
  - Includes possible study and leave opportunities; the World Resources Institute; and engagements accepted and not accepted, 1985-1990 (Box 3)
  - Includes engagements accepted, 1990; New York University economics department interoffice memoranda, budgets, and other correspondence; and Eastern Economic Association correspondence and other materials, 1977-1985 (Box 4)
  - Includes New York University economics department forms, tenure material, and other material, 1974-1982; correspondence with and manuscripts from Harcourt, Brace, Jonanovitch, Inc., 1982-1985; correspondence, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Includes recommendations, 1988-1989; proposals, books, and articles reviewed, 1981-1989; graduate student correspondence, salary information, and other materials from Princeton University, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Includes material for On Finances of the Performing Arts During Stagflation, 1980-1982; and National Science Foundation proposals reviewed and other NSF materials, 1981-1984 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence and material relating to Baumol's work on Fritz Machlup's book, 1982-1984; drafts of articles written for various journals, including the Journal of Political Economy, Journal of Law and Economics, and Journal of Economic Literature, 1976-1990 (Box 8)
  - Computer Diskettes containing graphs, publications, miscellaneous information, and system software (Box 9)
    [Electronic records are closed to use until migrated to a library server. To request access, please contact a reference archivist before coming to use this collection.]
  - Reel-to-reel audiotape: Velocidad Grabación-3 3/4, miércoles 11 de enero de 1978 [1978 Jan 11 Wed.], 15 minutos del día 12 Lado 2 [15 minutes of day 12, side 2] (Box 10)
    [Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Use of these materials may require production of listening or viewing copies. Please contact a reference archivist before coming to use this collection.]